

Rehmat Kumar

UI / UX Designer

WORK EXPERIENCE

Web Developer

2023 - Present

Bharat Intern

Currently, I am working with the Bharat Intern as a Web Developer. Bharat Intern gives me the experience and confidence for the industry out there. So far, I have learnt the concepts of HTML, CSS and Javascript and have implemented in the tasks provided.

Social Entrepreneur

2023

Hamari Pahchan NGO I Delhi

I am working with Hamari Pahchan NGO which provides a number of benefits to the needy including education, hygiene products, etc. Along with the technical side, I always want to work with the NGOs to make society a lot better than it is today.

Full Stack Development

2023 - Present

HomeGenie

HomeGenie is a user-friendly IoT based platform to connect all your IoT devices of your home so that you can control them from anywhere, as long as you have a proper internet connection for both your IoT devices and the device you are using HomeGenie with. The catch is, you dont even need to download any external application or software as it works on the browser. You can even give the voice commands like "Turn on the fan" or "Turn off the lights" and the IoT device will act accordingly.

Full Stack Development (Team Project)

2023 - Present

URide

Uride is a user-friendly platform specifically made for Chitkara students for their travelling issues. One of the biggest issues in the college was transportation. Some students come by their vehicles, some use public transport and other uses college transport. This inconsistency can be a big trouble when we look into factors like expenses, timings and most of all, hygiene. So our team came up with a project which can store the data of the day-scholars who can be labeled as "drivers" and "passengers". The students who come with their own vehicles can give a ride to the others just like popular services like Bla-Bla and Uber. Through this platform, students can easily choose their ride as a passenger and can further safely pay via razorpay (or cash) to the drivers. We have added a user-friendly map marking all the nearby locations of the university for easy access.

EDUCATION

Software Engineering Deakin University2021-2023

Computer Science Engineering Chitkara University 2023-Present

ABOUT ME

Hey, It's Rehmat here and I am a UI/UX designer with a good experience of full stack development. So far I have made some remarkable projects while studying in the reputed college. I always give my best in the workspace and try to learn more and more by each day.

CONTACTS

- + (ح
 - +91 79881-99822
- \bowtie
- rehmat3108@gmail.com
- **②**

rehmat-papneja

SKILLS

- UI/UX
- Full Stack Development
- C#, Embedded C/C++ programming
- Arduino, IoT, Robotics
- Leadership
- Project management